<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Source>
  <string-array name="descriptions">
    <item>It contains an assortment of highly artifacted images of dogs in various settings.</item>
    <item>It contains an image of a futuristic looking skyline, blanketed by a binary sunset.</item>
    <item>It contains a starchart. The attached date is corrupted.</item>
    <item>It contains a 30 page review of an old T-shirt with a stylized print consisting of a lunar body behind three howling dogs.</item>
    <item>It contains a video file showcasing two Urbworld gangs fighting for territory.</item>
    <item>It contains nothing. It is completely blank.</item>
    <item>It contains a slightly corrupted video file showcasing a Rimworld explorer watching a ship explode in the upper atmosphere.</item>
    <item>It contains a text file entitled 'Cryptosleep Revival Briefing'.</item>
    <item>It contains an image of an artist's impression of the anatomy of a Thrumbo.</item>
    <item>It contains a video file showcasing an advertisement for Glitterworld foot massages.</item>
    <item>It contains an old entertainment application depicting the management of a planetary colony.</item>
    <item>It contains an outdated ethics paper on the use of mechanical units in Urbworld crowd control.</item>
    <item>The decoding process has unfortunately damaged this datadisk beyond recovery.</item>
    <item>It contains videos of cats reacting badly to certain foods.</item>
    <item>It contains a series of image files that are too corrupted and unable to be viewed.</item>
    <item>It contains a series of text files. The contents appear to be scout reports on mechanoid movements.</item>
    <item>It contains a single audio file. Of what can be discerned, it appears to be a poor soul being accosted by mechanoids.</item>
    <item>It contains various handcrafted images of animals in their natural habitats.</item>
    <item>It contains an image of two people standing victorious, with a Thrumbo corpse in the background.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains an image of various animals inside cages.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains an image of rolling hills. In the distance, a mechanoid hive can be seen.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains a large amount of images of cats. The images have humourous text added to them.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains a slightly corrupted video file. The video shows mechanoids being lured into an ambush.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains someone's personal diary. The files are mostly corrupted. From what can be deciphered, the author of the diary was an unfortunate victim of a bandit attack.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains an assortment of extremely old entertainment applications.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains various images of what appears to be a marriage ceremony.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains an assortment of low quality images appearing to show UFOs.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains a video file. The video is security camera footage of a civilian ship. Towards the end of the video, the hull appears to rupture, apparently from an explosion from outside of the ship.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains a single video file. The video shows a meteorite striking a planet.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains various text files. They appear to be guides on how to correctly skin animals of various species.</item>
    <item>This datadisk contains a single, heavily corrupted video file. The video appears to show a group of rimworld explorers attempting to open a ruined structure. The video abruptly ends when the group creates an opening.</item>
  </string-array>
  
</Source>